Cooperative Recreation Service collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 4. Song indexes and copyright research, ca. 1930-1970
  - Song list, undated (Box-folder 101/8)
Davies, H. Walford. The New Fellowship Songbook. London: Novello and Company, Ltd, 1931.